Welcome back.
In our last session, you set the stage for a championship season.
This week, we get into the data.
In elite sports,
teams spend millions on scouting reports because you can't design a winning
game plan without first understanding the talent.
In leadership, the best coaches do the same.
This lesson is about becoming a student of your talent, but it starts with an honest
scouting report on yourself.
This is not about what you've heard before,
but what you condition yourself to do daily.
To coach your player, you must first lead yourself.
In our next video,
we'll start that process by creating your own leadership blueprint,
your M.V.P. plus V.